赵柯宇 Korey Zhao



高级前端/前端负责人(FE.M) 29岁(29 years old)

6年经验(6 years+)

四川·成都(SC·ChengDu)

kevu.zhao@foxmail.com

13730846784

自我评价

SELF-EVALUATION

六年开发经验,前端技术栈均有所涉猎。目前负责聚美优品电商、增长业务的前端团队,从独立模块开发、工程构建到团队管理都有一定的经验。自建技术博客,实现过一个基于 proxy 的 MVVM 框架,并在掘金(ID:korey)上发表过 webpack 源码和 vue 源码分析系列等前端技术文章,希望为社区做一些微小的贡献。

Six years of development experience, understand all FE technology stacks. Head of the FE team of Jumei e-commerce and growth. Have certain experience in independent module development, project construction and team management. Created a technical blog and a MVVM framework based on proxy, and published FE technical articles such as webpack and vue source code analysis series on JueJin (ID:korey), hope to make some small contributions to the community.

工作经验

2017.04 - 至今 聚美优品·成都

高级前端/前端负责人

- 。 高级前端, 后晋升为电商、增长团队前端负责人
- 。 负责架构底层及业务开发,提出技术解决方案
- 。 上线项目包括街电H5/小程序/CRM, 美点H5, 聚美优品/鹿尚生活/白金大脑小程序,增长H5, 刷宝H5等
- 。 技术栈涉及Vue, React, Electron, Webpack, 小程序, 快应用等

2015.06 - 2017.04 兰途科技

高级前端研发工程师

- 。 负责快速构建高质量移动APP/PC/H5页面
- 。 高度组件化、模块化思维,拥有各平台调试能力
- 。 技术栈涉及Angular, Vue, Cordova, Gulp等

2014.08 - 2015.06 卓煌企业

前端研发工程师

- 。 负责企业站静态页开发及后台维护
- 。 负责百度竞价操作及SEO优化
- 。 技术栈涉及jQuery等

教育背景

2010.09 - 2014.06 四月

四川工商学院(本科)

电子信息工程

主修课程: 数电, 模电, 单片机, 嵌入式, C语言等等。

WORK EXPERIENCE

2017.04 - now JUMEI

FE.TL

- Senior FE, promoted to TL of e-commerce and growth
- Support architecture and business development, propose solutions
- Online includes Jiedian H5/ MiniP / CRM, Meidian H5,
 Jumei/Lushang/Brain MiniP, Growth H5, ShuaBao H5, etc
- Technology stack includes Vue, React, Electron, Webpack, Mini program, Quickapp, etc

2015.06 - 2017.04 LANTU TECH

Senior FE.D engineers

- Responsible for developing APP/ PC/ H5 pages
- Componentization and modularization, debugging capabilities of each platform
- o Technology stack includes Angular, Vue, Cordova, Gulp, etc

2014.08 - 2015.06 ZHUO HUANG

Web front end development

- Responsible for enterprise static page development &
 maintenance
- Responsible for Baidu bid operation and SEO optimization
- o Technology stack includes jQuery, etc

EDUCATION

2010.09 - 2014.06 STBU (B.S.)

Electronic Information Engineering

Major: digital, analog, single-chip, embedded, C language, etc.

感谢您的阅读。了解更多: https://flqin.com